A Guide to the Asian Cultural Council records, Administrative Files, RG 1 FA427
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administrative, 1952, 1954-2006; 1; 108.25 Cubic Feet 246 document boxes.
  - ACC records, 1955-1958, 1960-2006; 2
    - Japan-U.S. Friendship Commission (JUSFC), 1976-1991; 6
      - Azechi, Takuji, 1985-1986, 1984-1986 (Box 239, Folder 4646)
      - Azechi, Takuji, 1985-1986, 1984-1986 (Box 248, Folder 4731)
      - Bara, Hikari, 1980-1981, 1980-1984, 1986-1987 (Box 239, Folder 4647)
      - Ehara, Tomoko, 1980-1981, 1980-1984, 1989 (Box 240, Folder 4648)
      - Hagiya, Kyoko, 1979-1980, 1982, 1984 (Box 240, Folder 4649)
      - Hayashi, Michiko, 1984-1985 (Box 240, Folder 4650)
      - Jin, Yuji, 1982-1983, 1980-1983 (Box 240, Folder 4651)
      - Kano, Mune, 1984-1985 (Box 240, Folder 4652)
      - Kataoka, Michihiro, 1979-1980 (Box 240, Folder 4653)
      - Kato, Tomoko, 1981-1982, 1980-1982, 1984 (Box 240, Folder 4654)
      - Kono, Hideo, 1979-1980, 1978-1981 (Box 240, Folder 4655)
      - Kuroda, Shigeki, 1984-1985 (Box 240, Folder 4656)
      - Kurosawa, Mikako, 1982-1983, 1982-1988 (Box 240, Folder 4657)
      - Kurosu, Hanako, 1983-1984, 1983-1986 (Box 240, Folder 4658)
      - Matsumura, Akira, 1983-1984, 1983-1985 (Box 241, Folder 4659)
      - Matsuno, Jun, 1980-1981, 1980-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 241, Folder 4660)
      - Matsuzaka, Tetsuo, 1985-1986, 1983-1986, 1988-1989 (Box 241, Folder 4661)
      - Mizumoto, Shuji, 1981-1982, 1981-1984 (Box 241, Folder 4662)
      - Mizumoto, Shuji, 1981-1982, 1981-1984 (Box 248, Folder 4732)
      - Morino, Mayumi, 1982-1983, 1979, 1982-1983 (Box 241, Folder 4663)
      - Morozumi, Osamu, 1985-1986 (Box 241, Folder 4664)
      - Murabayashi, Miyuki, 1981-1982 (Box 241, Folder 4665)
      - Ohta, Hajime, 1982-1983, 1981-1983 (Box 241, Folder 4666)
      - Otani, Shiro, 1980-1981 (Box 242, Folder 4667)
      - Sato, Toshiaki, 1981-1982, 1981-1984 (Box 242, Folder 4668)
      - Shirato, Hirotoshi, 1983-1984 (Box 242, Folder 4669)
      - Suga, Juiichiro, 1979-1980, 1980-1981 (Box 242, Folder 4670)
      - Suzuki, Takafumi, 1985-1986, 1985-1987 (Box 242, Folder 4671)
      - Takagi, Toshinori, 1983-1984, 1983-1985 (Box 242, Folder 4672)
      - Takahashi, Masaatsu, 1982-1983 (Box 242, Folder 4673)
      - Terada, Izumi, 1984-1985, 1984-1986, 1989 (Box 242, Folder 4674)
      - Tsuchiya, Alisa, 1985-1986 (Box 242, Folder 4675)
      - Uchida, Hideya, 1983-1984, 1983-1984, 1989 (Box 242, Folder 4676)
      - Uchida, Hideya, 1983-1984, 1983-1984, 1989 (Box 242, Folder 4676A)
      - Ushikubo, Ken'ichi, 1979-1980 (Box 242, Folder 4677)
      - Yokobori, Koji, 1980-1981, 1980-1991 (Box 243, Folder 4678)
      - Yoshitake, Takako, 1981-1982, 1977-1986 (Box 243, Folder 4679)
      - U.S. Government, 1976-1983 (Box 243, Folder 4680)
    - Out of Program, 1973-1982, 1984-1986; 7
      - A-Out of Program, 1974; 1976-1981 (Box 243, Folder 4681)
      - B-Out of Program, 1975-1981 (Box 243, Folder 4682)
      - C-Out of Program, 1976-1981, 1986 (Box 243, Folder 4683)
      - D-Out of Program, 1975-1981 (Box 244, Folder 4684)
      - E-Out of Program, 1976-1978, 1980, 1982 (Box 244, Folder 4685)
      - F-Out of Program, 1976-1980 (Box 244, Folder 4686)
      - G-Out of Program, 1975-1980 (Box 244, Folder 4687)
      - H-Out of Program, 1975-1981, 1987 (Box 244, Folder 4688)
      - I-Out of Program, 1976-1981, 1984 (Box 244, Folder 4689)
      - J-Out of Program, 1976-1980 (Box 244, Folder 4690)
      - K-Out of Program, 1976-1981 (Box 244, Folder 4691)
      - L-Out of Program, 1975-1980 (Box 244, Folder 4692)
      - Ma-Mc-Out of Program, 1976-1981 (Box 245, Folder 4693)
      - Me-Mu-Out of Program, 1976-1981 (Box 245, Folder 4694)
      - N-Out of Program, 1976-1980 (Box 245, Folder 4695)
      - O-Out of Program, 1976-1979 (Box 245, Folder 4696)
      - P-Out of Program, 1973-1974, 1976-1980, 1986 (Box 245, Folder 4697)
      - R-Out of Program, 1975-1981 (Box 245, Folder 4698)
      - Sa-Se-Out of Program, 1975-1981, 1981 (Box 245, Folder 4699)
      - Sh-Sn-Out of Program, 1976-1980 (Box 246, Folder 4700)
      - So-Sw-Out of Program, 1975-1981 (Box 246, Folder 4701)
      - T-Out of Program, 1975-1981 (Box 246, Folder 4702)
      - U-V-Out of Program, 1976-1979, 1981 (Box 246, Folder 4703)
      - W-Out of Program, 1975-1981, 1985 (Box 246, Folder 4704)
      - X-Y-Out of Program, 1975-1978, 1980 (Box 246, Folder 4705)
      - X-Y-Out of Program, 1975-1978, 1980 (Box 246, Folder 4705A)
    - Asian Cultural Council Annual Reports, 1980-1997; 8; 15 Bound Volumes 15 bound volumes
      Chronological
      Annual reports
      - ACC Annual Report 1980-1983 (Box REF 306 ASI 1983)
      - ACC Annual Report 1984 (Item REF 361.76 ASI 1984)
      - ACC Annual Report 1985 (Box REF 361.76 ASI 1985)
      - ACC Annual Report 1986 (Box REF 361.76 ASI 1986)
      - ACC Annual Report 1987 (Box REF 361.76 ASI 1987)
      - ACC Annual Report 1988 (Box REF 361.76 ASI 1988)
      - ACC Annual Report 1989 (Box REF 361.76 ASI 1989)
      - ACC Annual Report 1990 (Box REF 361.76 ASI 1990)
      - ACC Annual Report 1991 (Box REF 361.76 ASI 1991)
      - ACC Annual Report 1992 (Box REF 361.76 ASI 1992)
      - ACC Annual Report 1993 (Box REF 361.76 ASI 1993)
      - ACC Annual Report 1994 (Box REF 361.76 ASI 1994)
      - ACC Annual Report 1995 (Box REF 361.76 ASI 1995)
      - ACC Annual Report 1996 (Box REF 361.76 ASI 1996)
      - ACC Annual Report 1997 (Box REF 361.76 ASI 1997)